(Raj:)Uh, turn left here
and see if he turns with us.
(Penny:)Well, why is
he turning here?
(Penny:)The restaurant's the other way.
I don't know.
(Leonard:)He uses that traffic app.
Maybe there's an accident.
(Penny:)Oh, so follow him.
Oh, no!
I told you!
(Bernadette:)It's probably
just a coincidence.
(Bernadette:)Speed up a little,
see if he stays with you.
(Penny:)Well, go faster.
(Penny:)You're losing him.
What is his hurry?
(Howard:)You know what,
flash your lights.
(Penny:)Let him know it's you.
(Howard:)He's flashing his lights.
(Howard:)What's that mean?
I-I think he wants us
to pull over.
Do not pull over!
I'm not raising this baby alone!
Hang on!
(engine revving)
(Alfred:)So, after
your husband passed,
(Alfred:)you never remarried?
(Mary:)No, just focused on work
and the church.
(Alfred:)Ah. And what do you do?
(Mary:)I work at the church.
(Alfred:)Well, they're lucky
to have you.
MARY:
Well, thank you.